Right now, stretch your hand.
You demon, I order you to leave my people, right now.
I order you to leave my people!
Leave my people!
I order in the name of Jesus!
I order - with all your affliction,
with all your desease, with all your situation -
Leave my people!
Open your lips and begin to command that! Command that!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
There is fire in the house.
For you to be included you must let your offence go.
When you hold an offence in our heart, you are not included.
There is miracle, there is healing, there is deliverance going on.
There is blessing going on -
greater blessing, salvation, deliverance, breakthrough are moving around.
Atmosphere is full of breakthrough.
Atmosphere is full of blessing.
Atmosphere is full of healing.
When you hold an offence, you are not included.
This is Word for you before we move.
Think about it.
When you hold an offence in your heart, you are not included.
Watch your screen!
Do you see what is happening? That is the atmosphere we are in.
Atmosphere of healing,
atmosphere of miracle, breakthrough.
Now, when you hold an offence in your heart, you are not included.
Viewers at home, listen! Right now
in your home, anywhere you are.
Are you under the influence of my voice?
Here is miracle, here is deliverance, here is breakthrough.
Here is blessing, you can just tap it.
When you hold an offence in your heart, you are not included.
Right now, deal with your offence right now.
Pain in the past - deep pain.
Begin to ask God to release you, ask for release.
Begin to release yourself from deep pain.
Not just pain - deep one
There are some pain that are so deep: "Would I forget? Would I forgive?"
Deep pain...
Open your lips, begin to deal with this.
Viewers at home!
I am very very very sure, this offence has created wall between you and God.
Have you dealt with offence? I connect your heart, I connect your spirit.
Every pain, every pain in the past, every deep pain -
I release you in the name of Jesus!
I release you from every pain,
every insult,
every embarrassment,
every persecution,
every hatred.
Pain.
Pain in the past.
Pain in the past, deep bitterness -
be released!
Confess: "I am released!"
Open your lips and begin to release yourself.
I am released, in the name of Jesus!
Pain, pain, pain...
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Watch your screen!
In the name of Jesus Christ,
I separate you from every pain in the past.
Every embarrassment - be separated in the name of Jesus!
Whatever pain might have caused you, whatever nightmare - be delivered in the name of Jesus Christ!
Be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever hurt, hurt in the past,
deep hurt - be separated in the name of Jesus Christ!
I separate you from that nightmare!
In the mighty name of Jesus!
Do you know what is going on?
Ask yourself: "Do I understand what's going on?"
Ask yourself!
I can't hear you!
Ask yourself: "Do I understand what's going on?"
I believe, you don't understand...You don't understand what's going on.
- Stop what you are doing!
- You say what? - Stop it! Stop it!
She should not forgive. She should live with it for the rest of her life.
Do you understand what's going on ?
Are you sure? Let me see your faith.
If that's the way you want to express your faith, it's ok.
Faith is the thing of the spirit.
Let's carry on, let's go on.
Leave me alone. I'll destroy her, I'll destroy her!
Will you welcome the Holy Spirit mightly?
Oh, Holy Spirit we welcome You today,
Fill us with your presence as we give you the praise
Lord, we are Your temple, for You alone we wait,
Holy Spirit, welcome in this place,
Holy Spirit, come and take your place.
Oh Holy Spirit, we welcome You today,
Fill us with your presence as we give you the praise
Lord, we are Your temple for You alone we wait,
Holy Spirit, welcome in this place.
Holy Spirit come and take your place.
Holy Spirit, we welcome You today,
Fill us with your presence as we give you the praise,
Lord, we are Your temple, for You alone we wait,
Holy Spirit, welcome in this place.
Holy Spirit, come and take your place.
As we gather may Your Spirit dwell within us.
As we gather may we glorify Your name.
Knowing well that as our heats begin to worship,
We will be blessed because we came.
We'll be blessed because we came.
As we gather may Your Spirit dwell within us.
As we gather may we glorify your name.
Knowing well that as our heats begin to worship,
We will be blessed because we came.
We'll be blessed because we came.
Hallelujah!
Listen, this is the voice of God.
I order and command every demon that disturbs you, in the name of Jesus.
I order and command them out in the name of Jesus!
I command them out in the name of the Jesus!
I order and command them to leave you in the name of Jesus!
Leave my people, in the name of Jesus!
Leave my people with all your affliction!
Leave my people with all your sickness!
Leave my people with all your disappointment!
Leave my people with all your setback!
Say: "Leave me in the name of Jesus!"
Open your lips, prayer!
I am a great man. I have destroyed him!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
If you are free, you can know. You know, demon is a burden, - if you're free from this burden, you can know.
It's a thing of the spirit.
We are not fighting the flesh and blood
but spiritual beings.
I command you, demon, in the life of my people - leave them in the name of Jesus!
Listen, demon - leave my people, in the name of Jesus!
Leave my people, in the name of Jesus!
Leave my people in the name of Jesus!
You sickness, disease, affliction - in the blood, kidney, liver, in any part of your organs -
I command them to leave you in the name of Jesus!
You sickness, in any part of your organ.
Open your lips and begin to rebuke that sickness and disease.
Rebuke that sickness and disease.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
How did you enter her body? - I will not tell you!
You have come again. - Who are you in this body?
Who are you?
I said she is my wife!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Every inherited sickness in your blood, fluids, in every part of your organs -
begin to command them out!
Command them out!
Destroy, destroy! She can't serve God!
I will destroy everything! She can't serve God!
Darkness!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
I will leave you at the right time.
But we are about to get there.
I would not leave you to go with sickness.
The sickness you brought here today will not follow you.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
I speak to every organ in your system!
I speak to every organ, every faculty,
every organ of yours!
I command that sickness, I command that disease, I command that affliction.
I say - affliction!
I order you right now to leave my people!
Leave my people!
Open your lips and begin to rebuke that affliction!
Tell that affliction to leave you!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Viewers, where can you go from His presence?
I say to that affliction in every area of your organs, in a hidden place.
I command them out in the name of Jesus!
You affliction, you disease in the hidden places, - I say out!
I say out, leave my people!
Leave my people in the name of Jesus!
You affliction, you disease, you affliction, you disease, leave my people!
Leave my people! Leave my people!
Viewers, begin to confess your freedom.
I can see you being healed.
I can see you being saved.
I can see you being delivered.
I can see you being blessed.
I can see you being healed, being delivered.
Confess your freedom!
I am redeemed!
I am healed!
I am delivered!
I am healed, I am delivered!
Confess your freedom, freedom, freedom...
In Your presence - that's where I am strong.
In Your presence, oh Lord, my God!
In Your presence - that's where I belong.
Seeking your face, touching your grace
In the cleft of the rock.
In your presence, oh God.
In Your presence - that's where I am strong.
In Your presence, oh Lord, my God!
In Your presence - that's where I belong.
Seeking your face touching your grace
In the cleft of the rock!
In the presence of God!
In Your presence - that's where I am strong.
In Your presence, oh Lord, my God!
In Your presence - that's where I belong.
Seeking your face, touching your grace.
In the cleft of the rock.
In your presence, oh God!
Thank you, Lord. Give thanks to God, give thanks to Him!
Hallelujah, give thanks to Him!
In Jesus Christ name!
Right now be open to the Spirit of God.
Yes, He wants to contact you. He's concerned about you.
Tell your neighbour: "Jesus is concerned about me".
Jesus is concerned about me!
I can't hear you.
He wants you to be like any apostle
He has created.
He is concerned about you. He loves you, He loves you so much - more than you love yourself.
Jesus loves you more than you love yourself.
He is concerned about you. Are you ready?
Right now begin to take your career, business from where it is now to where Jesus wants it to be.
Open your lips right now. By faith, take your career, your business, finances
from where they are right now to Jesus wants it to be.
In Jesus Christ name we pray.
I command breakthrough to your life!
Your business - breakthrough!
Your career - breakthrough!
I say breakthrough!
Your efforts - breakthrough!
Your attempt - breakthrough!
Your desire - breakthrough!
Breakthrough!
I want to hear you shout: "Breakthrough!"
In Jesus' name!!!
Jesus is not a man that lies.
If He says 'yes' - no one can say 'no'.
If He says 'no' - no one can say 'yes'.
Jesus says 'breakthrough'.
I just want to see your belief.
Breakthrough!
Your belief is your response.
I say - breakthrough!
Breakthrough!
Hallelujah!
Believing is our connection. Just believe - you shall be saved, -
says the Lord.
That belief is your response.
At this moment, out there, you can respond to many things and you don't mean it.
You may shout 'hallelujah' but you don't really mean it.
But at this moment in His presence He is concerned about your response.
Whatever you say, so shall it be!
Breakthrough!
Hallelujah, I can hear from the Spirit of God.
He said to me I should say to you: "Just believe".
He is not saying: "Believe!" He says: "Just believe!"
There is a difference between 'believe' and 'just believe'.
He is begging you now.
Just believe - so shall it be, in Jesus' name.
Hallelujah.
Hallelujah!
Think about that: if Jesus is saying 'just believe', - He is concerned about you.
He knows you, He knows your disposition.
He knows you are weak. He wants to be your strength.
Tell your neighbour: "Just believe".
Just believe! I can't hear you! Just believe!
Just believe!
In this case now no one would leave here without being delivered.
Jesus says: "Just believe!" He is not saying 'believe', He says "Just believe!'
He is begging you. Just believe!
Hallelujah. What is your response now?
Just believe!
Viewers all over the world. Just believe!
Jesus says to you: "Just believe!"
Hallelujah!